http://www.focusonenergy.com/about/privacy-policy

COVID-19 Update: Read More >>
ResidentialAppliance RecyclingApplicationsEventsFree ProductsHeating and CoolingRenewable EnergyInsulation and Air SealingLightbulb DiscountsNew Home CertificationSmart ThermostatsFind an Energy AdvisorTrainingOnline MarketplaceBusinessAvailable OfferingsAgribusiness CustomersCommercial and Industrial CustomersSchool and GovernmentNew ConstructionRenewable Energy OptionsCatalogs and ApplicationsCustom ProjectsMultifamily Property OwnersParticipating UtilitiesWhere Do I Begin?Find an Energy AdvisorFind a Trade AllyTrainingTrade AllyBenefits of Being a Trade AllyBusiness Contractor ResourcesBusiness Equipment IncentivesCo-op Reimbursement FormCode of ConductLookup Check DetailsQualified ProductsResidential Contractor ResourcesTrainingFind an Energy AdvisorAbout UsAbout Focus on EnergyCommunity Outreach RequestEvaluation ReportsJob OpeningsParticipating UtilitiesPress ReleasesRequest for ProposalsResearch and PilotsSuccess StoriesUtility ResourcesTrainingBlogSearchEn español
COVID-19 Update: Read More >>
Residential
Appliance Recycling
Applications
Events
Free Products
Heating and Cooling
Renewable Energy
Online Marketplace
Take advantage of programs and products that help you save energy at home, and check to see if your utility offers incentives for participation.
Participating Utilities Find a Trade Ally Contractor
Business
Available Offerings
Agribusiness Customers
Commercial and Industrial Customers
School and Government
New Construction
Renewable Energy Options
Catalogs and Applications
Custom Projects
Multifamily Property Owners
Participating Utilities
Where Do I Begin?
Find an Energy Advisor
Find a Trade Ally
Training
Find energy-saving programs and incentives available for your business—no matter what industry you’re in.
Find Incentives Where Do I Begin?
Trade Ally
Benefits of Being a Trade Ally
Business Contractor Resources
Business Equipment Incentives
Co-op Reimbursement Form
Code of Conduct
Lookup Check Details
Qualified Products
Residential Contractor Resources
Training
Find an Energy Advisor
Grow your business by becoming a Trade Ally contractor or service provider specializing in energy efficiency.
Become a Trade Ally
About Us
About Focus on Energy
Community Outreach Request
Evaluation Reports
Job Openings
Participating Utilities
Press Releases
Request for Proposals
Research and Pilots
Success Stories
Utility Resources
Training
Blog
Have a big idea that you think could propel energy efficiency forward in Wisconsin? We'd like to hear it! It's your turn to help us create innovative solutions for the future.
Submit an Idea
Search
Looking for something specific on our site?
Have some questions?
Dig a little deeper in our Help Center.
Help Center
En español
Login
Register
Username
Password
Email Address
Username
Contact settings
Personal contact form
Allow other users to contact you via a personal contact form which keeps your email address hidden. Note that some privileged users such as site administrators are still able to contact you even if you choose to disable this feature.
Locale settings
Time zone
AbidjanAccraAddis AbabaAlgiersAsmaraBamakoBanguiBanjulBissauBlantyreBrazzavilleBujumburaCairoCasablancaCeutaConakryDakarDar es SalaamDjiboutiDoualaEl AaiunFreetownGaboroneHarareJohannesburgJubaKampalaKhartoumKigaliKinshasaLagosLibrevilleLomeLuandaLubumbashiLusakaMalaboMaputoMaseruMbabaneMogadishuMonroviaNairobiNdjamenaNiameyNouakchottOuagadougouPorto-NovoSao TomeTripoliTunisWindhoekAdakAnchorageAnguillaAntiguaAraguainaArubaAsuncionAtikokanBahiaBahia BanderasBarbadosBelemBelizeBeulah (North Dakota)Blanc-SablonBoa VistaBogotaBoiseBuenos Aires (Argentina)Cambridge BayCampo GrandeCancunCaracasCatamarca (Argentina)CayenneCaymanCenter (North Dakota)ChicagoChihuahuaCordoba (Argentina)Costa RicaCrestonCuiabaCuracaoDanmarkshavnDawsonDawson CreekDenverDetroitDominicaEdmontonEirunepeEl SalvadorFort NelsonFortalezaGlace BayGodthabGoose BayGrand TurkGrenadaGuadeloupeGuatemalaGuayaquilGuyanaHalifaxHavanaHermosilloIndianapolis (Indiana)InuvikIqaluitJamaicaJujuy (Argentina)JuneauKnox (Indiana)KralendijkLa PazLa Rioja (Argentina)LimaLos AngelesLouisville (Kentucky)Lower PrincesMaceioManaguaManausMarengo (Indiana)MarigotMartiniqueMatamorosMazatlanMendoza (Argentina)MenomineeMeridaMetlakatlaMexico CityMiquelonMonctonMonterreyMontevideoMonticello (Kentucky)MontserratNassauNew Salem (North Dakota)New YorkNipigonNomeNoronhaOjinagaPanamaPangnirtungParamariboPetersburg (Indiana)PhoenixPort of SpainPort-au-PrincePorto VelhoPuerto RicoRainy RiverRankin InletRecifeReginaResoluteRio BrancoRio Gallegos (Argentina)Salta (Argentina)San Juan (Argentina)San Luis (Argentina)SantaremSantiagoSanto DomingoSao PauloScoresbysundSitkaSt BarthelemySt JohnsSt KittsSt LuciaSt ThomasSt VincentSwift CurrentTegucigalpaTell City (Indiana)ThuleThunder BayTijuanaTorontoTortolaTucuman (Argentina)Ushuaia (Argentina)VancouverVevay (Indiana)Vincennes (Indiana)WhitehorseWinamac (Indiana)WinnipegYakutatYellowknifeCaseyDavisDumontDUrvilleMacquarieMawsonMcMurdoPalmerRotheraSyowaTrollVostokLongyearbyenAdenAlmatyAmmanAnadyrAqtauAqtobeAshgabatBaghdadBahrainBakuBangkokBarnaulBeirutBishkekBruneiChitaChoibalsanColomboDamascusDhakaDiliDubaiDushanbeGazaHebronHo Chi MinhHong KongHovdIrkutskJakartaJayapuraJerusalemKabulKamchatkaKarachiKathmanduKhandygaKolkataKrasnoyarskKuala LumpurKuchingKuwaitMacauMagadanMakassarManilaMuscatNicosiaNovokuznetskNovosibirskOmskOralPhnom PenhPontianakPyongyangQatarQyzylordaRangoonRiyadhSakhalinSamarkandSeoulShanghaiSingaporeSrednekolymskTaipeiTashkentTbilisiTehranThimphuTokyoTomskUlaanbaatarUrumqiUst-NeraVientianeVladivostokYakutskYekaterinburgYerevanAzoresBermudaCanaryCape VerdeFaroeMadeiraReykjavikSouth GeorgiaSt HelenaStanleyAdelaideBrisbaneBroken HillCurrieDarwinEuclaHobartLindemanLord HoweMelbournePerthSydneyAmsterdamAndorraAstrakhanAthensBelgradeBerlinBratislavaBrusselsBucharestBudapestBusingenChisinauCopenhagenDublinGibraltarGuernseyHelsinkiIsle of ManIstanbulJerseyKaliningradKievKirovLisbonLjubljanaLondonLuxembourgMadridMaltaMariehamnMinskMonacoMoscowOsloParisPodgoricaPragueRigaRomeSamaraSan MarinoSarajevoSimferopolSkopjeSofiaStockholmTallinnTiraneUlyanovskUzhgorodVaduzVaticanViennaVilniusVolgogradWarsawZagrebZaporozhyeZurichAntananarivoChagosChristmasCocosComoroKerguelenMaheMaldivesMauritiusMayotteReunionApiaAucklandBougainvilleChathamChuukEasterEfateEnderburyFakaofoFijiFunafutiGalapagosGambierGuadalcanalGuamHonoluluJohnstonKiritimatiKosraeKwajaleinMajuroMarquesasMidwayNauruNiueNorfolkNoumeaPago PagoPalauPitcairnPohnpeiPort MoresbyRarotongaSaipanTahitiTarawaTongatapuWakeWallisUTC
Select the desired local time and time zone. Dates and times throughout this site will be displayed using this time zone.
Picture
Your virtual face or picture.One file only.800 KB limit.Allowed types: png gif jpg jpeg.Images larger than 1024x1024 pixels will be resized.
CAPTCHA
Math question
9 + 3 =
MEASURE
~{ cart_item.measure }
~{cart_item.unit}
QUANTITY
INCENTIVE CODE
~{ cart_item.product_id }
INCENTIVE TOTAL
$~{ (cart_item.rebate_amount*cart_item.quantity).toFixed(2) }
Get Incentives
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience: Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
To improve our website: We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To improve customer service: Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To administer a promotion, survey or other site feature.
To send periodic emails: The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your interests, in addition to receiving occasional Focus on Energy news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
Do we use cookies?
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information to outside parties. We may release this information to trusted third parties who assist us in administering the Focus on Energy program, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third-Party Links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act
Pursuant We do not intend to collect, nor do we have actual knowledge that we do collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website is directed exclusively to individuals who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
www.focusonenergy.com&nbsp;1 S. Pinckney, Suite 340 Madison, WI 53703focusinfo@focusonenergy.com800.762.7077
